smileygamer.com 2012-12-05

# Privacy Policy - Smiley Gamer

| 

SmileyGamer.com respects the privacy of Internet users.  
In general, we receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, and communicating with you. This information will not be shared with third parties.

This website stores a harmless cookie in your browser, with non personally identifiable information, such as recently played games.

During the process of delivering an ad to you, no personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address is collected. However, some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use are obtained. The information collected are used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. Advertisers may use cookies to compile anonymous statistics about our visitors. You can "opt-out" of the behavioral advertising delivered by members of the Network Advertising Initiave, on their opt-out page: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We have contracted with ValueClick to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ValueClick and its business partners may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick, please see ValueClick's privacy policy at <http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>.

SmileyGamer.com respects the intellectual property rights of others and expects its users to do the same.  
Please report alleged copyright infringements on our site to admin (at) smileygamer.com.  
You can also contact that address for any other serious issues.

|
